https://lfcsmo.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Lutheran Family and Children's Services of Missouri
Guardianship
How Do I Locate My Birth Family?
FAQs
Are you pregnant and confused?
We can help!
Privacy Policy
LFCS values its visitors’ privacy. This privacy policy summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor, and what we will and will not do with it.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for lfcsmo.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. If you visit a web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
How policy changes are communicated.
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email list registration, email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request/donation.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to inform you of other opportunities, events, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can so at any time by emailing us or by calling 314/787- 5100.
External data storage sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for ‘https’ at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Changes to this Policy
We may make changes to this privacy notice from time to time. You may check back on this page at any time to see our current policy.
If you feel we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should immediately email us or call 314/787- 5100.
Receive our Emails
Find out more from your local office
Southwest OfficeMid-Missouri OfficeSoutheast OfficeSt. Charles OfficeSt. Louis OfficeHilltop
About Us
Our History
Events
Board Leadership
Staff Leadership
Partners
Our Commitment to Quality
Adoption
Make an Adoption Plan
Domestic Adoption
Intercountry Adoption
Guardianship
How Do I Locate My Birth Family?
More Adoption Information
Foster Care
Becoming a Foster Parent
Temporary Foster Care
Resources
Pregnant or Parenting
Pregnant and Need Help
Parenting and Need Help
LinkedIn
Lutheran Family and Children Services of Missouri (LFCS) serves nearly 50,000 people across the state each year. Learn more about our life-saving programs and how you can get involved now!
Phone: 866-326-LFCS
Locations: St. Louis Office, Southeast Office, Southwest Office, Mid-Missouri Office2018 990: PDF2019 Annual Report: PDFClient Rights and Responsibilities: PDFEEO Policy: PDF2019 Fall Spirit Newsletter: PDF Privacy Policy
©2020 Lutheran Family & Children's Services of Missouri
